



virajj014@gmail.com B-2, Sahib Parisar, Yadav Colony Jabalpur [M.P.]

https://harshalportfolio.vercel.app/

https://github.com/virajj014

ABOUT ME

I am a seasoned MERN Stack developer with 2+ years of experience as a Full Stack Mentor at GeeksForGeeks. I offer freelance web and app development services, delivering functional and visually appealing projects. I am passionate about learning and I believe it is the key to success.

SKILLS

- Frontend Development React JS, React Native, Next JS, Angular JS, Redux, HTML,
- Programming C , C++ , Python, DSA, OOPS, Networking
- Back End Development Node JS, Express JS, AWS, MongoDB, Django, SQL, GraphQl

WORK EXPERIENCE

Geeks For Geeks Mentor & Educator

Full Stack Mentor • 2021 - Present

- Built 50+ Live WEB & APP Development projects at GeeksForGeeks video content platforms.
- I work closely with the content creation team.
- Mentored 50k+ students
- https://www.youtube.com/@GeeksforGeeksWebDevelopment

Educate Bharat

Freelancing • 2023 (2 months)

- Built a complete educational platform with video streaming, quiz, pdf notes features.
- I used MERN Stack with React Native and AWS
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=com.educatebharat&hl=en_IN&gl=US

Kylo Apps

React Native Developer Intern • 2023 (1 month)

- Built Vyap ecommerce grocery app in react native
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.vyap_app

KoiReader Technologies

React Native Developer Intern • 2023 (3 months)

• Built KoiReader scanning app in React Native

App Xperts

Freelancing • 2023 (2 months)

- Built 2 Full Stack REACT JS websites
- https://catchyfive.com/
- https://makanmate.vercel.app/

Other...

React Native Developer Intern • 2022 -2023

- Dreamviewer infotech Built a MERN stack Backend for a Multi Level Marketing company.
- JP Techno Park Built Packers and Movers App (Logistics) Full Stack Mobile Application (React Native & Nodejs)
- Disha Softwares Built Pro Cart App (Food Delivery) Full Stack Mobile Application (React Native & Nodejs)

EDUCATION

B Tech in Computer Science in AIML - 7.8 CGPA

Gyan Ganga Institute of Technology Jabalpur • 2020-2024

High School (10 th) - 72%

Christ Church Boy's Senior Secondary School Jabalpur • 2004 –2018

Higher Secondary School (12 th) - 79%

Maharashtra English Medium School Jabalpur • 2018 –2020

CERTIFICATIONS

- Networking Cisco Network Essentials 2023
- Programming Programming Essentials in C++ (2020-24), Programming Essentials in C (AIML 2020-24)
- Web Development JavaScript Essentials 1 (JSE), Responsive Web Design Certificate by Free Code Camp
- Internships 3 Month React Native Internship Completion at KoiReader Tech, 1 Month React Native Internship Completion at Kylo Apps

All Certificates Link - https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1S_ftRwiblCszZ6iNuZUwtOy4TKPV2AGJ?usp=sharing